 {

      "category":
            "Nature",
      "questions":
          [
            {
               "answer": "North American beaver",
               "question": "What is the national animal of Canada?"
            },
            {
               "answer": "Golden eagle",
               "question": "What is the national animal of Albania?"
            },
            {
               "answer": "Pekingese",
               "question": "Which dog used to be sacred in China?"
            },
            {
               "answer": "Hives",
               "question": "Urticaria is a skin disease otherwise known as what?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "Whale",
               "question": "What kind of animal is the largest living creature on Earth"
             },
            {
               "answer": "Paleontology",
               "question": "Give another name for the study of fossils?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "Penguin",
               "question": "Which bird can swim but cannot fly?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "Mosquitoes",
               "question": "What do dragonflies prefer to eat?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "Hinny",
               "question": "What do you get when you crossbreed a donkey and a horse?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "Fleas",
               "question": "Which insects cannot fly, but can jump higher than 30 cm?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "Wisent",
               "question": "What is the name of the European Bison?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "Eel fish",
               "question": "What is called a fish with a snake-like body?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "Vienna",
               "question": "In which city is the oldest zoo in the world?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "Dogs",
               "question": "After which animals are the Canary Islands named?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "Maple",
               "question": "Which plant does the Canadian flag contain?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "Plankton",
               "question": "What is the food of penguins?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "Siberian tiger",
               "question": "Which is the largest species of the tiger?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "Deer Tick",
               "question": "The bite of which insect causes the Lyme Disease?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "Elephant",
               "question": "Which mammal cannot jump?"
             }
          ]
    }